<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cellscanner</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_header">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="tac_data_collection">
<![CDATA[
<p>
View online: https://sites.google.com/view/cellscanner/homepage
</p>

<h2>Purpose of Cellscanner</h2>
<p>
The purpose of Cellscanner is to collect and store network and location data.
When activated, Cellscanner logs the following types data:
<ul>
<li>addresses of cell towers the device connects to;</li>
<li>geo-coordinates along with meta data such as their accuracy; and</li>
<li>timestamps from the start and end of a call.</li>
</ul>
In addition, a device identifier is stored. This identifier is used to link different databases from
the same device, and is generated randomly, once after the app is installed.
Cellscanner may be configured to upload data to a remote server.
<b>No data is collected, stored or shared with us or anyone else without your explicit permission.</b>
</p>
]]>
    </string>
    <string name="tac_colophon">
        <![CDATA[
Cellscanner is developed by the Netherlands Forensic Institute (<a href="http://www.forensischinstituut.nl">www.forensischinstituut.nl</a>)
with support from the European Union&apos;s Horizon 2020 research and innovation program under grant agreement No. 833635 (project ROXANNE: Real-time network, text, and speaker analytics for combating organized crime, 2019-2022).
]]>
    </string>
    <string name="tac_about_app">
        <![CDATA[
<p>
<b>Cellscanner</b> requires the following permissions to operate.

<ul>
<li><b>Location access</b> is required to collect network or location information.</li>
<li><b>Phone state access</b> is required if call state logging is switched on, i.e. whether a call is active or not.</li>
</ul>
</p>
]]>
    </string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_accept">I understand and accept the terms and conditions as listed above</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_close">Close</string>
    <string name="valueBaseText">no data</string>
    <string name="prominent_disclosure_text">This app collects location data to enable collecting and storing network and location data even when the app is closed or not in use.</string>
    <string name="apply_settings_text">About to apply settings. Are you sure?</string>
</resources>
