<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cellscanner</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_header">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="tac_data_collection">
<![CDATA[
<p>This app is created by the Netherlands Forensic Institute to collect data for a dataset to be used in research and development and in legal cases.
The app collects two types of location data, namely information about the cell towers the sim card(s) connect to and GPS data.
The research done by the NFI will look at overall travel patterns generated by users of different devices versus users of the same device (i.e. two sim cards in one device).
To identify whether data originates from different devices or from a single device, the device\'s android ID is stored along with the data.
</p>
<p>
Although the NFI will not look at individual addresses or locations that may be visited, it should be noted that individual analysis of the collected data could reveal (frequently) visited addresses or locations, such as the person\'s home address.
</p>

<p>
By using this app you consent that the collected data:
<ul>
    <li>is stored on the internal NFI servers</li>
    <li>is transported to the NFI internal servers via a cloud service</li>
    <li>is used in research and development done by the NFI</li>
    <li>is used as part of a reference dataset
    (A reference dataset is a collection of data from volunteers (as is the case in this app) and/or from previous cases that can be used to provide a frame of reference for data found in future cases.
In this use case, the reference data is only used and reported on a high-level, meaning the reference data used cannot be traced back to individuals.)</li>
    <li>is stored for a period of 15 years. This period can be prolonged if the data is used as reference data in a legal case. When used as reference data, the data will be removed along with the case data when the statute of limitations is reached.</li>
</ul>
</p>
<p>
When using this app you are free to start/stop recording at any time using the switch button on the main screen. In addition, you are free to enable/disable GPS logging.
When the app is recording and GPS logging is turned off, only the cell tower data is registered.</p>
<p>If at any point you wish to retract your consent and have your data removed completely, an email can be send to <a href="mailto:fbda@holmes.nl">fbda@holmes.nl</a>.
In this email you should mention this app (Cellscanner) and your android ID.
</p>

]]>
    </string>
    <string name="tac_contact_information">
        <![CDATA[
        <b>Contact person</b><br/>
        Team Forensic Big Data Analysis (FBDA)<br/>
        <a href="mailto:fbda@holmes.nl">fbda@holmes.nl</a><br/>
<br/>
<b>Contact information NFI</b><br>
<i>Visiting Address:</i>
<br/>
Laan van Ypenburg 6<br/>
2497 GB Den Haag<br/>
<br/>
<a href="http://www.forensischinstituut.nl">www.forensischinstituut.nl</a><br/>
<a href="mailto:info@nfi.nl">info@nfi.nl</a><br/>
<br/>
Tel.:    <a href="tel:+31708886750">(070) 88 86 750</a><br/>
Fax:     <a href="fax:+31708886555">(070) 88 86 555</a><br/>
<br/>
<i>Postal Address:</i>
<br/>
Postbus 24044,<br/>
2490 AA Den Haag<br/>
]]>
    </string>
    <string name="tac_about_app">"
The app requires consent for collecting location data.
\"Cell info\" registers the provider of the sim card and the cell towers the sim card connects with. \"GPS location info\" collects latitude, longitude, accuracy, and altitude data using Google's location service.

Before exporting, the collected data is stored in a sqlite database on the device itself. Data is only collected when the \"recording\" switch is turned on. Currently, the data can only be exported by clicking \"Export data\" and sending it via email (or another available app of choice). The database can be removed from the device by clicking \"Clear data\". If this is done before exporting the data, the data cannot be recovered.
    </string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_accept">I understand and accept the terms and conditions as listed above</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_close">Close</string>
    <string name="valueBaseText">searching</string>
</resources>
