<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cellscanner</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_header">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="tac_data_collection">
<![CDATA[
<p>
View online: https://sites.google.com/view/cellscanner/homepage
</p>

<h2>Purpose of Cellscanner</h2>
<p>
The purpose of Cellscanner is to improve the legal system. It is developed by the Netherlands
Forensic Institute (NFI), one of the world&apos;s leading forensic laboratories. Its activities
include forensic interpretation of location traces from cell phones. To be able to understand what
may have happened in a criminal investigation, it is important to know how mobile networks behave
under different circumstances. To learn how these networks operate, and how to interpret their
traces in criminal cases, we need data from ordinary users. We will use these data to derive
aggregated statistics. We will never attempt to reveal the identity of individual users.
</p>

<h2>Data collection</h2>
<p>
When activated, Cellscanner logs two types of location data: addresses of cell towers the device
connects to, and optionally GPS coordinates along with other GPS data such as their accuracy.
Cellscanner only collects what is strictly necessary to achieve its goal. That includes network and
(optionally) GPS data. Network data may reveal the coarse location of the device, depending on the
number of cell towers in the area. In addition, a device identifier is stored. This identifier is
used to link different submissions of data from the same user, and is generated randomly, once after
the app is installed.
</p>

<p>
Optionally, these data are sent manually or automatically to the NFI or, alternatively, to a third
party if the user chooses to change the upload settings. Data submitted to the NFI may be used and
stored up to a maximum of 30 years after submission, after which they will be deleted.
We will never attempt to reveal the identity of individual users.
We will never sell your data or otherwise share your data with anyone else.
</p>

<h2>User control</h2>
<p>
As a user, you control how and when data are collected. You may enable or disable recording at any
time using the switch button on the main screen. In addition, GPS logging is optional and can be
enabled or disabled as well. When the app is recording and GPS logging is disabled, only cell tower
addresses are registered. The user may also configure if and how data are uploaded.
</p>

<h2>User consent</h2>
<p>
By using this app, you indicate that you understand and consent to the above. If you wish to revoke
your consent, and have your already uploaded data removed from NFI servers, you can delete the app
and email your deletion request to fbda@nfi.nl. In this email you should mention the name of this
app (Cellscanner) and your device identifier, which is shown below. This identifier is the only link
between you and your data. We recommend that you write it down, in case you may wish to revoke your
consent later.
</p>

<p>
In summary, by using this app you consent and understand that:
<ul>
<li>the data collected by this app are stored locally on your device;</li>
<li>these data are securely uploaded to and stored on NFI servers when you enable the upload feature;</li>
<li>these data are used by NFI as described above;</li>
<li>these data are retained by NFI for a maximum of 30 years;</li>
<li>you may revoke your consent at any time.</li>
</ul>
</p>
]]>
    </string>
    <string name="tac_contact_information">
        <![CDATA[
Netherlands Forensic Institute<br/>
Forensic Big Data Analysis<br/>
<a href="http://www.forensischinstituut.nl">www.forensischinstituut.nl</a><br/>
<a href="mailto:info@nfi.nl">fbda@nfi.nl</a><br/>
Tel.:    <a href="tel:+31708886750">+31 70 88 86 750</a><br/>
<br/>
<i>Visiting Address:</i><br/>
Laan van Ypenburg 6<br/>
2497 GB Den Haag<br/>
The Netherlands<br/>
]]>
    </string>
    <string name="tac_about_app">
        <![CDATA[
<p>
<b>Cellscanner</b> requires the following permissions to operate.

<ul>
<li><b>Location access</b> is required to collect network information.</li>
<li><b>Phone state access</b> is required if call state logging is switched on, i.e. whether a call is active or not.</li>
</ul>
</p>
]]>
    </string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_accept">I understand and accept the terms and conditions as listed above</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_close">Close</string>
    <string name="valueBaseText">no data</string>
    <string name="ssh_known_hosts">
        <![CDATA[
|1|e92Mxgy4C4EBLmOZfpJelgy03Kk=|TGGhvbfbB7z8rZljRUG8FyxqjVk= ssh-rsa AAAAB3NzaC1yc2EAAAADAQABAAABgQC1ELi87xHOh8no304t9t6XW4PGlMa8+q/opqF+YtjOWDyznKxtfdohOpP7Fg7jJ98OtBPYaDnqNdHqidqGRR7cZqAa3GImYry50+hEHvFaPo00OswhckOsYtA2N+W7iWUtK5DlgQHlQsbVGidYtk+TT2crMqnj9CcNgXY2tKhhM7K99FnSxPmr6hgw2l1DyeNQG8+RvRziOMOl2tYibzcnfLIH46mn1VIEks8PbZ3xrn+gzHsm9YhGqZUgBIeAwELizI4cuhn0FxABm1YWMfH74B3opWfvZGTm+5FXDt6A4y6l7ZvwQl2qS0GmVsp/3qDDy5/RIjcAhKdFAOd+FqcihDHGYYwufFgc5LVfxdcdFMzKeESxBz1/1zoKptPsT+LzzjNI1y9lSnzpll8U2AM3omejrl5aIMoa5yCG73hgmz2TXN2/NsSi9vyrthTYyqTzQM6wLMRtsLFzQ9jBtVpmMTjE6OPHhIuDrLK1LrsTVSF00XJVLXLF36JV5AGTl4U=
|1|u7dqlh9ixMlfgNEmFcL9mEDOiUo=|L5cNlzNaLJlFKjqlnTWtGstDEko= ssh-rsa AAAAB3NzaC1yc2EAAAADAQABAAABgQC1ELi87xHOh8no304t9t6XW4PGlMa8+q/opqF+YtjOWDyznKxtfdohOpP7Fg7jJ98OtBPYaDnqNdHqidqGRR7cZqAa3GImYry50+hEHvFaPo00OswhckOsYtA2N+W7iWUtK5DlgQHlQsbVGidYtk+TT2crMqnj9CcNgXY2tKhhM7K99FnSxPmr6hgw2l1DyeNQG8+RvRziOMOl2tYibzcnfLIH46mn1VIEks8PbZ3xrn+gzHsm9YhGqZUgBIeAwELizI4cuhn0FxABm1YWMfH74B3opWfvZGTm+5FXDt6A4y6l7ZvwQl2qS0GmVsp/3qDDy5/RIjcAhKdFAOd+FqcihDHGYYwufFgc5LVfxdcdFMzKeESxBz1/1zoKptPsT+LzzjNI1y9lSnzpll8U2AM3omejrl5aIMoa5yCG73hgmz2TXN2/NsSi9vyrthTYyqTzQM6wLMRtsLFzQ9jBtVpmMTjE6OPHhIuDrLK1LrsTVSF00XJVLXLF36JV5AGTl4U=
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="message_public_key">
        <![CDATA[
 	-----BEGIN PUBLIC KEY-----
 	MIIBIjANBgkqhkiG9w0BAQEFAAOCAQ8AMIIBCgKCAQEAu+YzSMrclzGuOzyvnFlQ
 	VadJSW6WNzEOvvj1WsZZl8VlctPOTHJ3JSsfjxSwzqB5cMeAWV+9rXyPzhjJuQQk
 	LokEMY3T/aDa3EcvqCOrSNs6F3lfmp+eaGSpZ8x7WU4npJYkpqpoB7K0b82lSG1V
 	5mEVzjCIJsmaqaoGiRWt+WaQ3sJYSo6lKjfN7qhb9CWW00kJhWzqu+Xp2gvMHQa8
 	YHjPNXbkSbIc9aS+K51STwZve8G9hEVcWschp4pHIwfnAKVMwOYv6dj51gJXyr0o
 	RDEmQesyM8AaBcrmg7ofWjXkKDIstitEW821a5bDYum9wRA3qr4PrhrHtBEPVV4R
 	pQIDAQAB
 	-----END PUBLIC KEY-----
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="prominent_disclosure_text">This app collects location data to enable collecting and storing network and location data even when the app is closed or not in use.</string>
</resources>
